animeprivate.com 2007-04-25

# AnimePrivate.com - Private Download Community

The following webpage outlines AnimePrivate.com's collection and use of personal information from it's users. AnimePrivate.com values the privacy of our members and users, we will never share any personal information of anybody who logs on to AnimePrivate.com with anyone. This includes your e-mail address, name, and location. Upon logging on to AnimePrivate.com such things as your IP address and hostname are logged for statistical and security reasons. 

Children's Privacy  
AnimePrivate.com does not knowingly collect personal data from children under the age of 13. We make reasonable efforts to prevent someone who is underage from joining as a member of AnimePrivate.com, and will not collect information from them. If AnimePrivate.com learns that a child under the age of 13 has become a member, we will close that child's account and delete any information collected about the child. 

Not withstanding the foregoing, AnimePrivate.com may choose to retain some personal information such as the child's e-mail address as a means to prevent the child from re-registering at our website. The Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) went into effect in April 2000, and as a result websites all over the world wide web had to change their standards to not collect any information from a child. 

Disclosing Information  
AnimePrivate.com may store and disclose personal information allowed or required by applicable law or when deemed advisable by us. This means that we may make disclosures that are necessary to conform to legal and regulatory requirements or processes and to protect the rights, safety, and property of AnimePrivate.com, users of the AnimePrivate.com website, and the public. 

Security  
At AnimePrivate.com we make reasonable efforts to protect personal information such as passwords and use technology such as encryption, access control procedures, firewalls, and physical security. We urge you to use a unique password with both letters and numbers to protect your account on AnimePrivate.com and it's affiliated websites. If others, including family, friends or other household members access and use the message board through your login credentials, you are responsible for the actions of that individual. Only in extreme cases will your account be fully terminated. 

Third Parties  
Third Party websites may collect information from users of AnimePrivate.com, this information will include your IP address, hostname, and information about your system to help us serve you better. These are purely used for statistical reasons, and will not be used in any way other then that. Some programs that may collect this information include: Nedstat and Webalizer. 

Website Policy Changes  
AnimePrivate.com reserves the right to change this, and any other policy located on our website at anytime without notifying our users. If you have any comments, questions, or concerns regaurding this policy, or any other policy you may send them to us at admin@AnimePrivate.com. 

By continuing to access AnimePrivate.com and any of it's affiliated websites and files, you are expressly and impliedly agreeing to all of the terms as stated above on this document. You also hereby affirm that you are in compliance with all Federal, State and Local laws in your place of residence concerning the contents of AnimePrivate.com, and are also in agreeance with our Legal Disclaimer and Terms of Use.
